Davis Lapkin | Computer Scientists

3 8043853794

■ davis.lapkin@colorado.edu

Professional Profile

Disciplined University of Colorado Boulder student with a focused ambition to work within the Computer Science field. Currently studying computer science at University of Colorado Boulder, I have built a sound knowledge of computer science learnt through studies and various projects. With a passion for computer science, I am well placed to start a career within the computer science field and add value to the industry.

Core Skills

- · Python, Java, C++
- · Microsoft Office Suite
- Teamwork
- · Time Management

- · Technical Writing
- · Organization
- Communication
- · Attention to Detail

Education

- Bachelor's degree | University of Colorado Boulder | Aug 2020 May 2024
- High School Diploma | Island Coast High School | Aug 2019 May 2020
- High School | Mills E Godwin High School | Sep 2016 Jun 2019

Career Summary

Nov 2021 - Nov 2022 The UPS Store, North Fort Myers, Florida

Store Associate

Outline

Responsible for assisting customers with shipping and office supply needs.

Apr 2021 - Jul 2021 CVS, North Fort Myers, Florida

Cashier

Outline

Provided guidance to customers with the shopping experience and checkout process.

May 2017 - Jul 2019 Camp Hilbert, Richmond, Virginia

Camp Counselor

Outline

Guided and ensured the safety of children in grades 1 and 2. Led children in various outdoor camp activities. Included eight weeks of summer camp from summer of 2017 through summer of 2019.

Aug 2016 - Mar 2018 Tuckahoe Little League, Richmond, Virginia

Umpire

Outline

Responsible for providing umpire service during games for little league softball and baseball.